NYSUT Publications 6174 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 21, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1979; Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb.- April
- Box: 21, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1979; Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Box: 21, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1978; Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Box: 21, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1979; Publication (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Box: 21, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1979; Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Box: 21, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1979; Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Box: 22, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1980; Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Notes: June- Apr.
- Box: 22, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Notes: Dec. 1979-June 1980
- Box: 22, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1979; Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Box: 22, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1982; Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Notes: Jan.- June
- Box: 22, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1981; Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Notes: Sept.- Dec.
- Box: 22, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1980; Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Box: 23, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1981; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Notes: March- Aug.
- Box: 23, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1981; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Box: 23, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: Aug. 1982-June 1983
- Box: 23, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Box: 23, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Box: 23, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Box: 24, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Box: 24, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan. June
- Box: 24, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1984; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Box: 24, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1988; Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Notes: Jan.- Sept.
- Box: 24, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Notes: June- Dec.
- Box: 24, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan.- May
- Box: 25, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1990; Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Box: 25, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1980-1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Box: 25, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Notes: Oct. 1988-March 1989
- Box: 25, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1991; Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Box: 25, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1990; Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb.- Dec.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 26)
  - New York Teacher, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    v.15:no.1 (1973:Sep.2)-v.16:no.5 (1974:Sep.29). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 27)
  - New York Teacher, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    v.16:no.6 (1974:Oct. 6)-v.17:no.18 (1975:Dec. 28). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 28)
  - New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    v.17:no.19 (1976:Jan. 11)-v.18:no.9 (1976:Oct. 31). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 29)
  - New York Teacher, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    v.18:no.10 (1976:Nov. 7)-v.19:no.4 (1977:Sep. 25). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 30)
  - New York Teacher, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    v.18:no.30 (1977:Apr. 3)-v.19:no.36 (1978:May 28). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 31)
  - New York Teacher, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    v.19:no.38 (1978:June 11)-v.20:no.37 (1979:May 27). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 32)
  - New York Teacher, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    v.20:no.38 (1979:June 3)-v.21:no.30 (1980:Mar.). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 33)
  - New York Teacher, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    v.21:no.31 (1980:Apr.)-v.22:no.43 (1981:Aug.). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 34)
  - New York Teacher, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    v.23:no.1 (1981:Sep. 6)-v.24:no.15 (1982). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 35)
  - New York Teacher, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    v.24:no.16 (1984:Jan.)-v.25:no.21 (1985:June). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 36)
  - New York Teacher, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    v.26:no.1 (1984:Sep. 3)-v.27:no.9 (1985:Dec. 23). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 37)
  - New York Teacher, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    v.27:no.10 (1986:Jan. 20)-v.28:no.21 (1987:June 27). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 38)
  - New York Teacher, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    v.29:no.1 (1987:Aug. 31)-v.29:no.21 (1988:June 20). 35mm, Positive.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 39)
  - New York Teacher, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    v.30:no.1 (1988:Sep.)-v.30:no.21 (1989:June). 35mm, Positive.
- NYSTA News Trends/NYSTA The Challenger, Publication (Box 40)
  - NYSTA News Trends, 1965-1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    v.1 (1965)-v.6 (1971). 16mm, Negative.
  - NYSTA The Challenger, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    v.1:no.1-36 (1971). 16mm, Negative.
- NYCT/NYSUT New York Teacher, Publication (Box 41)
  - NYCT/NYSUT New York Teacher, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    v.1:no.1-45 (1972). 16mm, Negative.
- NYSUT New York Teacher/UFT Bulletin, Publication (Box 42)
  - NYSUT New York Teacher/UFT Bulletin, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    v.33:no.1 (1991:Sep. 2)-v.34:no.19 (1993:June 14). 16mm, Negative.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 43)
  - New York Teacher, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    v.35:no.1 (1993:Sep. 6)-v.35:no.21 (1994:June 13). 16mm, Negative.
- New York Teacher, Publication (Box 44)
  - New York Teacher, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    v.36 (1994-1995). 16mm, Negative.